<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="quad_stretch">Step 1: Stand with your back flat against the wall and your feet about 1-2 feet away from the wall.\n\nStep 2: Hold your arms at your sides or across your chest.\n\nStep 3: Bend at the knees and lower yourself down until your your thighs are parallel to the ground.\n\nStep 4: Hold this position for the desired time.</string>
    <string name="right_side_plank_crunch">Step 1: Lie on an exercise floor mat, face down.\n\nStep 2: Press your toes against the floor and place your hands flat on the ground shoulder width apart, fingers extended forward.\n\nStep 3: Push yourself up so that your arms are nearly extended and your torso and legs are off the floor. This is your starting position.\n\nStep 4: Inhaling, bend your arms to lower your body and touch your chest nearly to the floor.\n\nStep 5: Exhaling, contract your chest as you push off the ground and return to the starting position.\n\nStep 6: Pause for a moment and then repeat for a full set.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_circle">Step 1: Lie down on the floor. Your back should be flat and your knees bent at an approximately 60 degree angle.\n\nStep 2: Keeping your feet flat on the floor, cross your wrists over your chest. This is the starting position.\n\nStep 3: Bring your upper body up so that your shoulder blades are just off the floor and your body forms a C-shape. Exhale as you do so and hold the contraction for a second.\n\nStep 4: Slowly move down to the starting position. Exhale as you do so.\n\nStep 5: Repeat for the desired number of reps.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_push_up">Start in a standard pushup position with your hands slightly wider than shoulder-width apart and elbows completely locked out. Shoot your hips towards the ceiling and plant your toes into the ground so your body looks like an upside-down \'V. \' Slowly lower the top of your head towards the ground.</string>
    <string name="straight_armp">Start on all fours with wrists directly under shoulders, toes on the floor. Then, step one foot back and then the other as you engage abs and straigthen legs. Press the floor away from you with hands. You should form a straight line from shoulders to heels. Hold for 30 to 60 seconds</string>
    <string name="wall_exercise">Stand on left leg with back to wall about 3 feet away, ball of right foot pressed into wall, hands together at chest. Bend left knee and lower into a lunge (as shown). Return to start for 1 rep. Do 20 reps. Switch sides; repeat</string>
    <string name="push_up">Step 1: Lie down on the floor. Your back should be flat and your knees bent at an approximately 60 degree angle.\n\nStep 2: Keeping your feet flat on the floor, cross your wrists over your chest. This is the starting position.\n\nStep 3: Bring your upper body up so that your shoulder blades are just off the floor and your body forms a C-shape. Exhale as you do so and hold the contraction for a second.\n\nStep 4: Slowly move down to the starting position. Exhale as you do so.\n\nStep 5: Repeat for the desired number of reps.</string>

</resources>